<idea-plugin>
  <id>com.Sensorjang.plugin.Code2QRcode.id</id>
  <name>Code2QRcode</name>
  <version>2.1.3</version>
  <vendor email="515310624@qq.com" url="http://sensorjang.cn:81/">Sensorjang.cn</vendor>

  <description><![CDATA[
      This is a tool that can help developers easily share the code in the IDEA when they need it.<br>
      Developers can select the code and click to generate a QR code, which is convenient for sharing the code quickly and accurately. Recipients can use any QR code recognition tool to extract the results.<br>
      It supports viewing the generated QR code in the ToolWindow and saving the QR code in PNG format to the local disk.<br>
      It also supports creating web sharing links, burn-after-reading web sharing links (i.e., one-time links), and using custom passwords to restrict access to web sharing content.<br>
      The content shared via the web can support the display of Java, Python, C/C++, GO, MarkDown, Json, Bash, plain text, and other formats.<br>
      It supports generating web QR codes to enable scanning and jumping to the content sharing page.<br>
      <br>
      <em>Now supports [Chinese] and [special characters]</em>
      <br><br>
      这是一款可以帮助开发者在需要便捷分享IDEA内代码的工具。<br>
      开发者可以选中代码后一键生成二维码，便于快速精准得进行分享代码，接受者可以使用任意二维码识别工具提取结果。<br>
      支持在ToolWindow中查看生成的二维码、保存二维码格式为PNG图片到本地磁盘中。<br>
      支持创建web分享链接、阅后即焚web分享链接，并且支持对web分享的内容使用自定义密码限制访问。<br>
      通过web分享的内容可以支持Java、Python、C/C++、GO、MarkDown、Json、Bash、文本等格式展示。<br>
      支持生成web二维码，实现扫码跳转到内容分享页面。<br>
      <br>
      <em>现在已经支持[中文]和[特殊字符]</em><br>
    ]]></description>


  <change-notes><![CDATA[
      Version 2.1.3, this version includes the main functions of the original version: generating any QR code, displaying QR codes in the ToolWindow, and saving PNG images to the local disk.<br>
      It supports creating web share links, one-time web share links (i.e., once links), and password protection for web-shared content.<br>
      The web-shared content can be displayed in formats such as Java, Python, C/C++, GO, MarkDown, Json, Bash, and plain text.<br>
      It supports Chinese characters and special characters.<br>
      Compared to version 2.1.2, it adds the ability to generate web QR codes for scanning and jumping to the content sharing page.<br>
      <br>
      <em>Added the ability to generate web QR codes for scanning and jumping to the content sharing page</em><br>
      <em>Added a prompt for successful saving of PNG images to the local disk</em><br>
      <em>Improved stability and user interaction experience</em><br>
      <br><br>
      2.1.3版本，此版本包含原始版本的选择任意二维码生成、在ToolWindow展示二维码、保存png图片到本地磁盘的主体功能<br>
      支持创建web分享链接、阅后即焚web分享链接（也即once link），并且支持对web分享的内容使用自定义密码限制访问。<br>
      通过web分享的内容可以支持Java、Python、C/C++、GO、MarkDown、Json、Bash、文本等格式展示。<br>
      支持中文和特殊字符。<br>
      相对于2.1.2版本，新增生成web二维码，实现扫码跳转到内容分享页面功能。<br>
      <br>
      <em>新增生成web二维码功能、实现扫码跳转到内容分享页面，并支持保存png图片到本地磁盘</em><br>
      <em>新增png图片保存到磁盘成功的提示</em><br>
      <em>优化稳定性和用户交互体验</em><br>
    ]]>
  </change-notes>


  <!-- please see https://www.jetbrains.org/intellij/sdk/docs/basics/getting_started/build_number_ranges.html for description -->
  <idea-version since-build="212.0"/>


  <!-- please see https://www.jetbrains.org/intellij/sdk/docs/basics/getting_started/plugin_compatibility.html
       on how to target different products -->
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>


  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <!-- Add your extensions here -->
    <toolWindow id="Code2QRcode" factoryClass="com.sensorjang.CodeToQRcode.window.QRcodeShowWindowFactory" anchor="right" icon="/img/CodeToQRcode.svg"/>
  </extensions>


  <actions>
    <group id="Code2QRcode" text="Code2QRcode" popup="true">
      <add-to-group group-id="EditorPopupMenu" anchor="first"/>
      <action id="Code2QRcode_ac" class="com.sensorjang.CodeToQRcode.action.PopupAction" text="generate QRcode" description="Generate a PNG file containing a QR code (Code2QRcode) for the selected code and save it to a local disk">
        <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default" first-keystroke="control alt Q"/>
      </action>
    </group>
  </actions>

</idea-plugin>