<idea-plugin>
  <id>com.Sensorjang.plugin.Code2QRcode.id</id>
  <name>Code2QRcode</name>
  <version>2.1</version>
  <vendor email="515310624@qq.com" url="http://sensorjang.cn:81/">Sensorjang.cn</vendor>

  <description><![CDATA[
      This is a tool that can help developers easily share the code in the idea when they need it.<br>
      Developers can select the code and click to generate a QR code, which is convenient for sharing the code quickly and accurately. Recipients can use any QR code recognition tool to extract the results.<br>
      In addition, it supports viewing the generated QR code in toolwindow and saving the QR code in PNG format to local disk.<br>
      It also supports creating web sharing links, burning after reading web sharing links (i.e. once link), and supports using custom passwords to restrict access to web sharing content.<br>
      The content shared through the web can support the display of Java, Python, C/C++, GO, MarkDown, Json, Bash, text and other formats.<br>
      <br>
      <em>Chinese and special characters are not supported at the moment</em>
      <br><br>
      这是一款可以帮助开发者在需要便捷分享IDEA内代码的工具。<br>
      开发者可以选中代码后一键生成二维码，便于快速精准得进行分享代码，接受者可以使用任意二维码识别工具提取结果。<br>
      支持在ToolWindow中查看生成的二维码、保存二维码格式为PNG图片到本地磁盘中。<br>
      支持创建web分享链接、阅后即焚web分享链接，并且支持对web分享的内容使用自定义密码限制访问。<br>
      通过web分享的内容可以支持Java、Python、C/C++、GO、MarkDown、Json、Bash、文本等格式展示。<br>
      <br>
      <em>暂不支持中文和特殊字符</em><br>
    ]]></description>


  <change-notes><![CDATA[
      2.1 version, this version includes the main functions of selecting any QR code generation, displaying the QR code in ToolWindow, and saving to local disk for the original version<br>
      In addition, on the basis of the original version, it supports creating web sharing links, burning after reading web sharing links (i.e. once link), and supports using custom passwords to restrict access to web sharing content.<br>
      The content shared through the web can support the display of Java, Python, C/C++, GO, MarkDown, Json, Bash, text and other formats.<br>
      Compared with version 2.0, version 2.1 deletes useless dependencies, reduces the size of the installation package, and is convenient for developers to install.<br>
      <br>
      <em>Save as PNG picture</em><br>
      <em>You can select any line of code (generally no more than 30 lines are recommended)</em>
      <em>Support sharing your code through web links, and support password protection content, burning after reading web sharing links (i.e. once link),</em><br>
      <br><br>
      2.1版本，此版本包含原始版本的选择任意二维码生成、在ToolWindow展示二维码、保存到本地磁盘的主体功能<br>
      此外，在原有版本基础上新增支持创建web分享链接、阅后即焚web分享链接（也即once link），并且支持对web分享的内容使用自定义密码限制访问。<br>
      通过web分享的内容可以支持Java、Python、C/C++、GO、MarkDown、Json、Bash、文本等格式展示。<br>
      相对于2.0版本，2.1版本删除了无用的依赖项，减小了安装包的体积，便于开发者安装。<br>
      <br>
      <em>保存格式为PNG图片</em><br>
      <em>可以选择任意行代码(通常不建议大于30行)</em>
      <em>支持通过web链接分享你的代码，并且支持密码保护内容、阅后即焚web分享链接（也即once link）</em><br>
    ]]>
  </change-notes>


  <!-- please see https://www.jetbrains.org/intellij/sdk/docs/basics/getting_started/build_number_ranges.html for description -->
  <idea-version since-build="173.0"/>


  <!-- please see https://www.jetbrains.org/intellij/sdk/docs/basics/getting_started/plugin_compatibility.html
       on how to target different products -->
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>


  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <!-- Add your extensions here -->
    <toolWindow id="Code2QRcode" factoryClass="com.sensorjang.CodeToQRcode.window.QRcodeShowWindowFactory" anchor="right" icon="/img/CodeToQRcode.svg"/>
  </extensions>


  <actions>
    <group id="Code2QRcode" text="Code2QRcode" popup="true">
      <add-to-group group-id="EditorPopupMenu" anchor="first"/>
      <action id="Code2QRcode_ac" class="com.sensorjang.CodeToQRcode.action.PopupAction" text="generate QRcode" description="Generate a PNG file containing a QR code (Code2QRcode) for the selected code and save it to a local disk"/>
    </group>
  </actions>

</idea-plugin>